big927fm.com 2012-06-05

# 92.7 BIG FM Radio - India's Biggest FM Radio Station Network | 92.7 BIG FM Radio in 45 cities all over India..

|    
---  

**General Statement**  
Reliance Broadcast Network Limited (RBNL) including its subsidiaries and affiliates (hereinafter collectively referred to as “BIG 92.7 FM”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy provides concisely, the manner in which your data is collected and used by BIG 92.7 FM. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the BIG 92.7 FM website, you agree to the collection and use of your data by BIG 92.7 FM in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

BIG 92.7 FM respects the privacy of its listeners and users and is committed to protect it in all respects. The term User implies a visitor who has navigated to the website and who becomes a registered user of [www.big927fm.com](http://www.big927fm.com/) after registering on the website by providing all the relevant information as is mandated on the website. BIG 92.7 FM values the users of its website and is committed to safeguard the information it receives and maintains about them via the website. BIG 92.7 FM does not sell information about the users of its website, to others.

This certification applies to all sites/channels under the Reliance Broadcast Network Limited domain.  
**USE**

With a view to offer a most enriching and a holistic internet experience to the users of its website, BIG 92.7 FM offers a vast repository of online sites and variety of services. You may read the About Us section to know more about BIG 92.7 FM at <http://www.big927fm.com/AboutUs.php>. The contents of the site are made available to the visitors/ users for free but you shall need to complete the registration process to surf the site in detail. The information about the user as collected by BIG 92.7 FM is:

  1. information supplied by users and
  2. information automatically tracked while navigation (Information).

To avail certain sites/ services on our website, you would be required to provide some personal information for the registration process viz: -

  1. your name, 
  2. email address, 
  3. birth date, 
  4. gender, 
  5. zip code, 
  6. occupation, industry and 
  7. personal interests etc. The more information you volunteer and the more accurate it is, the better we are able to customize your experience on [www.big927fm.com](http://www.big927fm.com/).

**Use of Cookies**  
To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES:**  
Website of **BIG 92.7 FM** includes links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with **BIG 92.7 FM** , we may contact you from time to time about updation of your content to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit you. 

**OTHER INFORMATION**  
All information gathered on **BIG 92.7 FM** is securely stored within the **BIG 92.7 FM** controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access. 

However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. ****

BIG 92.7 FM may combine personal information collected from you with information from other services or third parties to provide a better user experience, to provide the services you've requested, that display customized content and advertising including customizing content for you. In case of up gradation of services, research and analysis, technological advancement, where we hire third parties for our aid and assistance, we require that they comply with our privacy policy by taking appropriate confidentiality and security measures. **BIG 92.7 FM** may also share the information with any third party, in limited circumstances, for national security and integrity or on an Order from any Court or competent authority.

Technical details in connection with visits to this website are logged by us and/or our internet service providers for our statistical purposes. No information is collected that could be used by us to identify website visitors. The technical details logged are confined to the following items:

  1. the IP address of the visitor’s web server 
  2. the top-level domain name used (for example .it, .com, .org, .net);
  3. the previous website address from which the visitor reached us as in search; 
  4. clickstream data which shows the traffic of visitors around this web site (for example pages accessed and documents downloaded) 
  5. the type of web browser used by the website visitor.

**BIG 92.7 FM** will make no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details listed above with any individual. The technical information will be used by **BIG 92.7 FM** only for statistical and other administrative purposes. You should note that technical details, which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection.

**USE BY CHILDREN**

**BIG 92.7 FM** does not encourage children to access this website. If you are under 18, you may do so with the involvement of a parent or guardian. **BIG 92.7 FM** absolves itself from any liability, damage, harm or loss, if the children falsely represent as being over the age of 18.

**CONDITIONS OF USE AND REVISIONS**

As we will attempt to constantly upgrade our website, the terms and conditions and privacy policy will appropriately change. To be abreast about the latest terms and conditions and privacy policy, we expect that you check and visit our web-site frequently.

This statement relates to our privacy practices in connection with this website. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to The Vice President Legal & Company Secretary, Reliance Broadcast Network Limited, 401, 4th Floor, Infiniti, Oshiwara, Link Road, Andheri (West), Mumbai 400 053 or by calling our board number at (022) 3068 9444.
